Guide to the Ithaca Rotary Club Records, 1914-2016.
Ithaca Rotary Club Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca Rotary Club Records, 1914-2016.
3067
Rotary Club of Ithaca (Ithaca, N.Y.)
28.7 Cubic Feet.
Correspondence, publications, photographs, videotapes, phonographs, CD's, DVD’s, scrapbooks, memorabilia, and artifacts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records created or assembled by the Rotary Club of Ithaca, New York. Including correspondence, publications, and material related to the functioning and activities of the club.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Ithaca Rotary Club was founded in 1914 by Edward G. Wyckoff, a prominent Ithaca businessman inspired by the Rotary movement and its ideals of fellowship and service. The club was the first Rotary club in the country founded without sponsorship from an established club, and it did not fully join the broader Rotary International organization until 1915. Ithaca Rotary has sponsored programs such as the Student Exchange, and has supported numerous organizations and causes, both throughout the Ithaca community and internationally. Ithaca Rotary has also sponsored the formation of additional Rotary clubs, including the Ithaca Sunrise Rotary Club, the Ithaca-Cayuga Rotary Club, and clubs in Dryden and Trumansburg, NY. Women have been members of Ithaca Rotary since Rotary International first allowed women in 1987. For more information, please see Margaret Hobbie's A BRIEF HISTORY OF THE ITHACA ROTARY CLUB (1995), Box 17, folder 15.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records created or assembled by the Rotary Club of Ithaca, New York. The collection includes correspondence, reports, minutes, memoranda, bylaws, secretarial and presidential files, membership records, Board of Directors records, annual reports, financial records, photographs, audiovisual material, oral histories, and a scrapbook. Publications of the Ithaca Rotary Club include bound and unbound issues of THE ROTARY CLUB NEWS (weekly publication), and pamphlets. The collection contains additional publications such as newsletters, convention proceedings and books from Rotary International, newsletters from Rotary Districts, publications from other Rotary clubs and a songbook. Audiovisual material consists of a videotape, CDs, floppy disks, DVDs and a phonograph. Ephemera and memorabilia include plaques, certificates, news clippings, and miscellaneous artifacts.
The majority of material in this collection dates from the 1950’s through 1980’s. A few items date back to the founding and early years of the organization. More recent material consists largely of photographs, meeting minutes and issues of THE ROTARY CLUB NEWS.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rotary Club of Ithaca (Ithaca, N.Y.); Rotary International; Rotary Foundation
Titles:
Rotary Club News
Subjects:
Rotary clubs--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Social service--New York (State)--Ithaca.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.)--Societies, etc.; Ithaca (N.Y.)--Social life and customs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Proceedings.; Minutes.; Newsletters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Administrative
Constitutions and Bylaws
Committees
General Administrative Records
Ithaca Rotary Charitable Trust
Club and Member History
Attendance Records
Rosters and Membership
Series II. Board of Directors
Series III. Presidents
Maurice C. Bond, 1971-1972
Ted Baldwin, 1963-1964
Ralph Hospital, 1964-1965
Eugene Erickson, 1986-1987
Barbara Thuesen, 1997-1998
Fred Antil, 2001-2002
President's Notebook
Series IV. Secretaries
General Secretaries, 1946-1974
Oliver “Ollie” Jones, 1946-1966
Frank R. Bliss, 1963-1964 and 1966-1970
Robert H. “Bob” Head, 1971-1980
Series V. Districts
Series VI. Rotary Foundation
Series VII. Ithaca Rotary Club Publications
Series VIII. Rotary International
General
Publications
Series IX. Multimedia
Series X. Photographs
Series XI. Memorabilia and Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administrative.
  Contains records pertaining to the administration of the Ithaca Rotary Club.
  - Constitutions and Bylaws
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1934, 1936, etc., 1934-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Section of Ithaca Rotary Constitution (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional Amendments and Revisions, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Constitution--Territory Amendments for Ithaca -Cayuga Club., 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Constitution/Bylaws (Barlow Ware), 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Constitution and Bylaws General (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Standard Interact Club Constitution and Bylaws, Vestal NY, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws, Ithaca NY, 2003, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Committees
    - Committee Reports, 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Committee Reports, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Committee Reports: Education Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Committee Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Committee Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Reports of Committee Chairmen: June 1, 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Committee Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Committee Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Programming Committee, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Committee Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Committees and Committee Reports, 1952-1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Student exchange committee (Greeting Cards), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Special Events Committee/Group Exchange Committee, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Rural-Urban Relations Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Rotary 4-H Horse Show., 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Rural-Urban Relations Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Rural-Urban Relations Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Programming Committee Binder, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Vocational Services Committee Binder (Barbara Thuesen), 1994-1995; 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Nominating Committee, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - General Administrative Records
    - Misc. Administrative Documents, Correspondence, 1935-2006, 1935-2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Administrative History, No Date (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Administrative Material, Spring, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Budgets, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Budget Planning Documents, Early 1970's (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 4-H Thank-you's, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Relinquishment of Territory for Ithaca-Cayuga Club, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Seven Lakes Girl Scout Council, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Ambassadorial Scholars, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Seventy-fifth Anniversary Material, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Barlow Ware's File, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Summary of Club Plans and Objectives for Rotary International, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - "Minute Book", 1914 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Oral History Project, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Programs, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Youth Soccer, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Adopt-A-Highway, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Share the warmth, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - To the membership, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Annual jobs, 2005-2009 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Grant files, 2000's (Box 34)
    - Insurance, 2000's (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Planning guide, 2009-2012 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Contracts, 2001-2010 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - New member flow coordinator - training packet, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Memorial gifts - Tompkins County Public Library Foundation, 2004-2007 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Pass the Gavel program, June 25, 2014 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Retention, 2001-2012 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Sergeant-at-arms, Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - General files (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - e-mails, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Tompkins Public Library, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - IRC trip to Mississippi, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - eTompkins Rotary Club, 2011-2013 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Budget FY 2011-2012, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Semiannual Report, 1999, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Rotaract, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Polio fundraiser, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Meeting Agendas, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Meeting Agendas, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Meeting Agendas, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Group study exchange with Taiwan, 2012 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Letters to club Presidents, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Misc. files, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Misc. meetings, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Additional grant files and general administration, 2000's (Box 38)
    - 2010-2011 club binder, 2010-2011 (Box 39)
    - Procedures Manual, 2015 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Task Force report and assorted secretarial documents, 2014-2015 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Ithaca Rotary Club records, 2011 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Ithaca Rotary Club records, 2015-2016 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Vocational Services, 1999=2011 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Ithaca Rotary Charitable Trust
    - Ithaca Rotary Charitable Trust Binder, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - I.R.C.T. President, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - I.R.C.T. minutes and applications, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - I.R.C.T. E*Trade, 1998-2005 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - I.R.C.T. Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - I.R.C.T. Investment policies and procedures, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - I.R.C.T. Contributions and other info and history, 1980-1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Fidelity Growth: IRCT, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Misc. I.R.C.T., 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Misc. I.R.C.T., 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Misc. I.R.C.T., ca. 1996-2011 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Club and Member History
    - Report of Addresses Delivered at the Banquet of the Rotary Club of Ithaca, New York, given in honor of the honorable Roger Butler Williams, Sr.", 1916 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Lou Bement, 1921-1932 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - 60th Anniversary Background Material, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Autobiography of Evan Jervis Morris, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Memoirs: Rev. Edward Horn III (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - 90th Anniversary Material, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Centennial, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - "A Brief History of the Ithaca Rotary Club", 2011 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Ithaca Rotary Club, 49 years, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Attendance Records
    - Attendance Sheets/Reports, 1924-1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Attendance Sheets/Reports, 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Attendance Sheets/Reports, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Secretary's Notebook: Attendance Records, 1971-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Rosters, 1931-1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - District 7170 attendance reports, 2005-2012 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Attendance, documents, 1996, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Rosters and Membership
    Includes dated and undated rosters and membership cards, loose pages from rosters, and information gathered for creating the rosters.
    - Roster Questionnaires, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Rosters, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - New Member Numbers, 1959-1960, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Roster Info, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Membership: Notes and Roster Material, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Rosters, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Rosters, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Rosters, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Rosters, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Rosters, 1998-2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Undated Roster Sheets (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Undated Rosters (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Undated Rosters (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Membership cards, 1966-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Membership cards, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Membership cards, 1966-1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - District 7170 membership rosters, 2001-2002 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Ithaca NY rosters, 1946-1947 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Rosters/directories, 1995-2004 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Rosters/directories, 2005-2012 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Membership surveys, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Membership committee material, 2003-2006 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Membership cards (4 small binder), Undated (Box 35)
- Series II. Board of Directors
  Board of Directors meeting minutes. Also includes some material presented to the Board, including correspondence and financial reports.
  - 1947 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 1948 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 1949 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 1951 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1953 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 1954 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 1955 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 1959 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 1960 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 1961 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1962 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 1964 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 1965 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 1966 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 1968 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 1970 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 1971 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Rotary Board Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Report to Board of Directors, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Art Kulp's Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Board of Direct. Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Financials (Board of Dir.), 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Rotary Club Minutes (BOUND VOLUME), 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club Minutes (BOUND VOLUME), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Rotary Club Minutes (BOUND VOLUME), 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Rotary Club Minutes (BOUND VOLUME), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2012-2014 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2014-2016 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2011-2015 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2010-2011 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Board of Director Minutes, 2011-2012 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Board of Director Minutes and account balances, 2014-2015 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Series III. Presidents
  The series consists largely of material from presidents’ notebooks/workbooks, including correspondence, material for the Board of Directors, budgets, reports and committee materials.
  - Maurice C. Bond, 1971-1972
    Includes material pertaining to the formation of the Ithaca-Cayuga Club.
    - Pres. Maurice C. Bond, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ted Baldwin, 1963-1964
    - Pres. Ted Baldwin, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Ralph Hospital, 1964-1965
    - Pres. Ralph Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Eugene Erickson, 1986-1987
    - Pres. Eugene Erickson's Book 1, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Pres. Eugene Erickson's Book 2, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Pres. Eugene Erickson's Book 3, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Barbara Thuesen, 1997-1998
    - Barbara Thuesen President's Notebook, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fred Antil, 2001-2002
    - Fred Antil's Folder, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - President's Notebook
    - President's Notebook, 2002-2004 (Box 32)
    - President's Notebook, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - President's Notebook, 1 of 2, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - President's Notebook, 2 of 2, 2008-2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - President's Notebook, 1 of 3, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - President's Notebook, 2 of 3, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - President's Notebook, 3 of 3, 2009-2010 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Series IV. Secretaries
  Contains the files assembled by secretaries of the Ithaca Rotary Club. These files cover a broad range of subjects, including membership and attendance, committees, club programming, material related to specific presidents and treasurers, and material pertaining to Rotary in a broader sense, including Rotary International, the Rotary Foundation, and the various Rotary districts of which Ithaca Rotary has been a member.
  - General Secretaries, 1946-1974
    This series begins with material from Earl Atkinson (1923-1946) and Frank Philipps (1946). It also includes material from a time of secretarial transition (1968-1974). When Secretary Frank R. Bliss died suddenly in 1970, several secretaries held the post in quick succession, including Clarence W. Mitchell, William H. Allen, Jr., and Robert “Bob” Head. Unlike other secretarial files, which are arranged according to secretary, the organizer of these files sorted them by years and topics, combining material from Bliss and the secretaries who followed him within each file. Finally, the series also includes one box of files (1944-1967) organized alphabetically rather than by subject. For instance, a file labeled “T” could contain material from the club treasurer, correspondents whose name begins with T, etc. This material is largely from Ollie Jones’ tenure, but also includes some material from Frank Philipps' time as secretary.
    - Earl Atkinson, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Frank Philipps, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Student Exchange, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Rotary International and District Remittances, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - New Members, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Secretary, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - President, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Rotary Bills, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Meeting Notes (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Misc Secretarial Material, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer: Reports to P. Brainard, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Ladies Night, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Rotary Near-by Clubs, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - R.I., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Rotary Foundation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Rotary Dues, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Members Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Secretary's Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - President Joe P. Bail, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Jap[anese] Group Study, 10/16-20, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Dist. Governor Brigham Thomson, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Committees, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Rotary International, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bulletins, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Directors: Material for Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Student Exchange, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Secretary's Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Reports to Treasurer, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - President: Richard Pollock, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Committee Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Material for meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Secretary, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Treasurer, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - President, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Programming Committee, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Rotary Material, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Attendance and Financial, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Attendance, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Secretary File, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - C, 1959-1965 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - D, 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - E, 1956-1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - F, 1948-1960 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - G, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - H, 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - I, 1950-1962 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - J, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - K, 1948-1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - L, 1948-1960 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - MC, 1947-1952 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - M, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - N, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - O, 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - P, 1947-1964 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Q, 1951-1955 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - R, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - S, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - T, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - U, 1945-1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - A, 1954-1962 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - B, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - D, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - E, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - F, 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - G, 1945-1965 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - H, 1955-1966 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - I, 1947-1964 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - J, 1954-1964 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - K, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - L, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - M, 1948-1965 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - MC, 1960-1965 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - N, 1947-1962 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - O, 1954-1958 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - p, 1951-1965 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Q, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - R, 1947-1965 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - S, 1951-1965 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - T, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - U, 1955-1959 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - V, 1951-1964 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - W, 1955-1965 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - X-Y-Z, 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - T-U-V, 1945-1954 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - M-N-O-P, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - P, 1945-1946 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - W-X-Y-Z, 1944-1962 (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - T, 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Treasurer's Report, 2013-2015 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Treasurer (job description), Undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Secretary's Report, 2013-2016 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Secretary's Report, 2006-2012 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Assistant Secretary, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Secretarial staff, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Secretary's Procedures, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Secretary job descriptions and review, ca. 1999-2012 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Oliver “Ollie” Jones, 1946-1966
    Jones was secretary of Ithaca Rotary from 1946-1963, and again from 1964-1966. In 1963-1964, he was District Governor of Rotary International District 717. This series contains some of his files as District Governor, as well as those during his transition back to his role as secretary of Ithaca Rotary.
    - Oliver Jones, 1945-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Budgets, 1947-1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Jones Secretary correspondence, etc., 1948-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Ollie Jones, 1951-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Correspondence, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Birthdays, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Assembly, 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Rotary Fellow, 1957-1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Correspondence and Notes, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Deposits, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Rotary Foundation, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Committee Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Oliver Jones, Sec'y, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Committees, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - District 717--Oliver Jones, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)